Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education In Asia Records, Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- New File -- Addendum, Series III
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
    - Publicity/Reports
      - Miscellaneous; statements and articles related to history of U.B.C.H.E.A., incl. by B.A. Garside, Wm. P. Fenn, and Eric North, 1922-1973 (Box 74, Folder 963)
- College Files -- Addendum, Series IV
  Materials are included from the following institutions:
  Hong Kong
  Chung Chi College
  Hong Kong Baptist College
  India>
  Ewing Christian College
  Indonesia
  Christian University of Indonesia
  Petra Christian University
  Satya Wacana (Satya Watjana)
  Japan
  International Christian University
  Korea
  Ewha Womans University
  Soong Jun University
  Yonsei University
  Pakistan
  Kinnaird College for Women
  The Philippines
  Central Philippine University
  De La Salle University
  Philippine Christian College
  Silliman University
  Taiwan
  Soochow University
  Tainan Theological College
  Tunghai University
  The files for these institutions are subdivided according to the following categories, as required by the amount of material:
  Administrative
  Academic
  Consolidated General File
  Periodical Publications
  Publicity/Reports
  - Hong Kong
    - Chung Chi
      - Board of Governors--Minutes, 1953-1964 (Box 110, Folder 1508-1510)
      - Building Committee--Minutes, 1955-1959 (Box 110, Folder 1511)
      - College Council Meetings, 1955-1958 (Box 110, Folder 1512)
      - College Council--Minutes, 1959-1964 (Box 110, Folder 1513-1516)
      - Development Plan for Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 1517)
      - Establishment of Chung Chi College, 1954-1957 (Box 110, Folder 1518)
      - Executive Committee of the Board-- Minutes, 1954 (Box 110, Folder 1519)
      - Hong Kong Government Post-Secondary Colleges Ordinance and Grant Regulations, 1959 (Box 110, Folder 1520)
      - Hong Kong Government Post-Secondary Colleges Ordinance and Grant Regulations, 1959-1960 (Box 111, Folder 1521)
      - Joint Meeting of the Board of Governors and the College Council, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1522)
      - Mission Board Secretaries Conference on Chung Chi, 1955 (Box 111, Folder 1523)
      - Ordinance/Constitution (Revised in 1968), 1955 (Box 111, Folder 1524)
      - Organization Chart, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 1525)
      - Planning Committee--Minutes, 1955 (Box 111, Folder 1526)
      - Presidents' Reports: Lee, Y. L., 1952-1953 (Box 111, Folder 1527)
      - Presidents' Reports: Lin, D. Y., 1955-1958 (Box 111, Folder 1528)
      - Presidents' Reports: Roy, Andrew T., Acting Pres., 1960 (Box 111, Folder 1529)
      - Presidents' Reports: Yung C. T., 1961-1964 (Box 111, Folder 1530-1531)
      - Presidents' Reports: Miscellaneous, 1968-1974 (Box 111, Folder 1532-1535)
      - Sub-Committee on Housing and Special Building Gifts, 1957 (Box 111, Folder 1536)
      - Theological Council--Minutes, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 1537)
      - U.B.C.H.E.A. Annual Neeting, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 1538)
      - Working Party on Educational Policy and University Structure, 1974-1975 (Box 111, Folder 1539-1541)
      - Calendars, 1955-1972 (Box 112, Folder 1542)
      - Calendars, 1973-1981 (Box 113, Folder 1543)
      - Handbook for New Students, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 1544)
      - Terms of Service, 1967 (Box 113, Folder 1545)
      - Orientation, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 1546)
      - Commencement, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 1547)
      - Conference for Teachers of English as a Second Language, 1962-1963 (Box 113, Folder 1548)
      - Opening Ceremony of the Athletic Field, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 1549)
      - Pre-Employment Workshop, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 1550)
      - Chung Chi Theological Seminary, 1966 (Box 113, Folder 1551)
      - Fehl, Noah E. - "History and Society" (Box 113, Folder 1552)
      - Young, Pauline V. - "How Can Social Research Serve the Community?", 1966 (Box 113, Folder 1553)
      - A general (Box 114, Folder 1554-1555)
      - Academic Calendar, 1960-1961, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 1556)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on the Establishment of Chung Chi College, c. 1954 (Box 114, Folder 1557)
      - Alumni Association, 1956-1973 (Box 114, Folder 1558)
      - Anderson, Dr. S. R. (and Olive L.), 1955-1958 (Box 114, Folder 1559)
      - Architectural Plans, 1955, 1957 (Box 114, Folder 1560)
      - Asian Cultures Program, Books on, etc., 1963-1964 (Box 114, Folder 1561)
      - Au, David R. K. (see also: file in RG 14), 1952-1960 (Box 114, Folder 1562-1564)
      - Auditor's Reports, 1954-1963 (Box 114, Folder 1565-1567)
      - B general (Box 114, Folder 1568)
      - Barr, Dr. and Mrs. John S. (see also: Faculty Openings), 1958-1963 (Box 114, Folder 1569)
      - Board of Governors, 1953-1975 (Box 114, Folder 1570-1571)
      - Books for Integrative Basic Studies, Proposal for, 1967-1968 (Box 114, Folder 1572)
      - Bookstore, 1965-1973 (Box 114, Folder 1573)
      - Brown, Dr. Howard, 1960-1962 (Box 114, Folder 1574)
      - Budgets and Budget Requests (see also: Financial Statements), 1953-1964 (Box 114, Folder 1575-1578)
      - Building--General, 1962-1969 (Box 114, Folder 1579)
      - Building Fund/Program, 1956-1959 (Box 114, Folder 1580)
      - Building Program--Student Dormitories, 1955-1966 (Box 114, Folder 1581)
      - Buildings--Residence Hall for Single Staff, 1966-1967 (Box 114, Folder 1582)
      - C general (Box 115, Folder 1583)
      - Chan, Cheung Ring (Samuel Chan), 1960-1967 (Box 115, Folder 1584-1588)
      - Chan, Daphne, 1957-1959 (Box 115, Folder 1589-1590)
      - Chan, Florence Suit Yin, 1956-1962 (Box 115, Folder 1591-1592)
      - Chan, Hok-lam (William), 1963 (Box 115, Folder 1593)
      - Chang, Hson Mou, 1970, 1974, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 1594)
      - Chang, Shu Ting, 1959, 1960, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 1595)
      - Chapel, 1959-1973 (Box 115, Folder 1596)
      - Chaplain, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 1597)
      - Coffield, Michael V., 1962 (Box 115, Folder 1598)
      - College Council--Minutes, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 1599)
      - Conference, Staff, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 1600)
      - Constitution and By-laws, 1954-1972 (Box 115, Folder 1601)
      - Cost, Student, 1963 (Box 115, Folder 1602)
      - D general (Box 115, Folder 1603)
      - Downer, Sara, 1956, 1959 (Box 115, Folder 1604)
      - Downie, Myra M., 1961-1962 (Box 115, Folder 1605)
      - E general (Box 115, Folder 1606)
      - Eldridge, Ann Linwood, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 1607)
      - Endowment Funds, College Policies on, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 1608)
      - English, Courses in, 1959 (Box 115, Folder 1609)
      - English Department, Needs of, 1958-1959 (Box 115, Folder 1610)
      - English Teaching: As a Second Language, Requirements, Facilities, etc., 1964, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 1611)
      - Espy, John L., 1959-1974 (Box 115, Folder 1612-1613)
      - Exchange Professors, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 1614)
      - F general (Box 116, Folder 1615)
      - Faculty--General, 1961-1972 (Box 116, Folder 1616)
      - Faculty Housing, 1961-1964 (Box 116, Folder 1617)
      - Faculty Openings, 1961-1974 (Box 116, Folder 1618-1619)
      - Faculty--Overseas Personnel Correspondence, 1964-1975 (Box 116, Folder 1620)
      - Faculty--Overseas Personnel Lists, 1964-1975 (Box 116, Folder 1621-1622)
      - Faculty Rules and Regulations, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 1623)
      - Faculty and Staff Liats, 1952-1960 (Box 116, Folder 1624)
      - Faculty and Staff Provident Fund (Retirement Fund), 1961 (Box 116, Folder 1625)
      - Faculty and Staff Salaries, 1958-1972 (Box 116, Folder 1626)
      - Faculty--Tutors, 1964-1971 (Box 116, Folder 1627)
      - Faucett, Lawrence Scholarahips, Books, Etc., 1962 (Box 116, Folder 1628)
      - Fehl, Ethel J., Bursar, 1960-1965 (Box 116, Folder 1629)
      - Fehl, Nosb E. (World History Project), 1962-1969 (Box 116, Folder 1630)
      - Fellowships, 1961-1974 (Box 116, Folder 1631)
      - Feng, S. C., 1956 (Box 117, Folder 1632)
      - Finance Budget Requests, 1964-1975 (Box 117, Folder 1633-1635)
      - Financial Statements, 1961-1966 (Box 117, Folder 1636-1637)
      - Financing, Memorandum on, 1957 (Box 117, Folder 1638)
      - Fitzwater, Bruce E., 1969-1970 (Box 117, Folder 1639)
      - Formation and Development, 1951-1960 (Box 117, Folder 1640-1641)
      - Founders' Day, 1967, 1971 (Box 117, Folder 1642)
      - Founding and Opening, Special Bulletins on, 1955-1956 (Box 117, Folder 1643)
      - G general (Box 118, Folder 1644)
      - Gilfillan, Edward, 1968-1970 (Box 118, Folder 1645)
      - Graduates, Lists of, 1955-1965 (Box 118, Folder 1646)
      - Graduation Ceremonies, 1956-1965 (Box 118, Folder 1647)
      - H general (Box 118, Folder 1648)
      - Hall, R. O. (Rt. Rev.), 1953-1959 (Box 118, Folder 1649)
      - Harvard-Yenching Grants, 1960-1971 (Box 118, Folder 1650)
      - Hillila, Dr. Ruth-Ester, 1965-1971 (Box 118, Folder 1651)
      - Historical Indices Project, 1964, 1965, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 1652)
      - History and Information, 1951-1972 (Box 118, Folder 1653)
      - Ho, Harold, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 1654)
      - I general (Box 118, Folder 1655)
      - Illick, Dr. J. Theron, 1954-1957 (Box 118, Folder 1656-1657)
      - J general (Box 118, Folder 1658)
      - Jefferson, Gary Hall, 1966-1968 (Box 118, Folder 1659)
      - K general (Box 118, Folder 1660)
      - Kilborn, Leslie G., 1958-1963 (Box 118, Folder 1661-1662)
      - Kong, Pearl, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 1663)
      - L general (Box 119, Folder 1664)
      - Lao Yung Vei, 1968-1970 (Box 119, Folder 1665)
      - Lau Oi Vah, 1970, 1971 (Box 119, Folder 1666)
      - Lay Voo Pok, 1965 (Box 119, Folder 1667)
      - Leary, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur, 1964-1967 (Box 119, Folder 1668)
      - Lee Raa Hon, 1970-1975 (Box 119, Folder 1669-1670)
      - Lee, Lyon (Nai Yuan), 1958-1970 (Box 119, Folder 1671-1673)
      - Liang, Chi Sen, 1962-1968 (Box 119, Folder 1674-1675)
      - Library--Building, 1964-1971 (Box 119, Folder 1676)
      - Library--Correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box 119, Folder 1677)
      - Library, Reports on, 1959-1971 (Box 119, Folder 1678)
      - Library--Search for Librarian, 1964-1968 (Box 119, Folder 1679)
      - Lin, D. Y., President, 1955-1956 Aug (Box 119, Folder 1680-1681)
      - Lin, D. Y., President, 1956-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1682-1689)
      - Lin, D. Y.--Addresses, 1956-1958 (Box 120, Folder 1690)
      - Lin, D. Y.--Reports, 1955, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 1691)
      - Lin, Ya-lan Tsui (Mrs. D. Y. Lin), 1956-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1692)
      - Loo, Dorothy King Duen, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 1693)
      - Lo, Po Yiu, 1964 (Box 121, Folder 1694)
      - M general (Box 121, Folder 1695)
      - Maung, Marya Webster, 1958, 1960-1963 (Box 121, Folder 1696)
      - McComb, Donald P., Bursar, 1966-1971 (Box 121, Folder 1697)
      - Missionaries on Staff, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 1698)
      - Music Department, 1964-1968 (Box 121, Folder 1699)
      - N general (Box 121, Folder 1700)
      - Newsletter, 1970-1972 (Box 121, Folder 1701)
      - Ng, Lee Ming, 1966-1975 (Box 121, Folder 1702)
      - Ng, Pedro Pat-Tao, 1966-1968 (Box 121, Folder 1703)
      - Ng, Pedro Pat-Tao, 1969-1971 (Box 122, Folder 1704-1705)
      - Noren, Loren E., Comptroller, 1957-1960 (Box 122, Folder 1706-1709)
      - O general (Box 122, Folder 1710)
      - Olley, Dr. John W., Theology Division, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1711)
      - Orientation Material., 1964, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1712)
      - P general (Box 122, Folder 1713)
      - Pang, S. H., 1956 (Box 122, Folder 1714)
      - Philosophy of Life Program, 1963, 1965 (Box 122, Folder 1715)
      - Pong, Rev. James T. N., 1954-1956 (Box 122, Folder 1716)
      - Pott, James H., 1955-1956 (Box 122, Folder 1717-1720)
      - Q general (Box 123, Folder 1721)
      - R general (Box 123, Folder 1722)
      - Rayne, Robert N., 1964-1967 (Box 123, Folder 1723)
      - Redlands Student Exchange, 1961-1962 (Box 123, Folder 1724)
      - Registrar's Report, 1952-1960 (Box 123, Folder 1725-1726)
      - Relocation of Village Families, 1958-1963 (Box 124, Folder 1727)
      - Research Institute of Far Eastern Studies, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 1728)
      - Roy, Andrew T., 1954-1967 (Box 124, Folder 1729-1742)
      - Roy, Andrew T., 1968-1972 (Box 125, Folder 1743-1744)
      - Runyan, Dr. Mary Edith, 1964-1970 (Box 125, Folder 1745)
      - Rutherford, Lexia P., 1966 (Box 125, Folder 1746)
      - S general (Box 125, Folder 1747)
      - Scholarships, 1958-1968 (Box 125, Folder 1748-1750)
      - Scholarships, 1969-1971 (Box 126, Folder 1751)
      - Shen, Phillip, 1953-1974 (Box 126, Folder 1752-1754)
      - Sheng, David, 1964-1965 (Box 126, Folder 1755)
      - Sprague, Mrs. Lloyd, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 1756)
      - Story Telling Project, 1962-1963 (Box 126, Folder 1757)
      - Student Expenses, 1960 (Box 126, Folder 1758)
      - Student Lists, 1956-1958, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 1759)
      - Student Statistics, 1951-1973 (Box 126, Folder 1760)
      - T general (Box 126, Folder 1761)
      - Tang, Jimmy Wah Piu, 1958-1960 (Box 126, Folder 1762-1763)
      - Tenth Anniversary, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 1764)
      - Theological Seminary Buildings, 1963, 1966-1969 (Box 126, Folder 1765)
      - Theological Seminary: Chair in Theology, 1972-1973 (Box 126, Folder 1766)
      - Theological Seminary: Consultation on Theological Education, 1968-1969 (Box 126, Folder 1767-1769)
      - Theological Seeinary: Correspondence, 1962-1974 (Box 126, Folder 1770)
      - Theological Seminary: Formation and Development, 1958-1971 (Box 126, Folder 1771)
      - Tompkins Report, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 1772)
      - Tonge, Rev. Walton, 1965-1968 (Box 126, Folder 1773)
      - Tschang, Hsi Lin, 1967-1969 (Box 126, Folder 1774)
      - Tse, Chui Rit, 1957-1959, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 1775)
      - Tunghai University, Cooperation with, 1970 (Box 126, Folder 1776)
      - Tutor Programs, 1970 (Box 126, Folder 1777)
      - Tyau, P. R. C., 1957-1960 (Box 126, Folder 1778)
      - U general (Box 126, Folder 1789)
      - Visitors, 1958-1960, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 1790)
      - W general (Box 127, Folder 1791)
      - Walline, E. E., 1952-1956 (Box 127, Folder 1792)
      - Wan, Grace Lee Tze-Huen, 1969-1971 (Box 127, Folder 1793)
      - Wong, S. T., 1956 (Box 127, Folder 1794)
      - Y general (Box 127, Folder 1795)
      - Yang, J. Y., 1955 (Box 127, Folder 1796)
      - Yue, Kwok Keung, 1964-1966 (Box 127, Folder 1797)
      - Yung, C. T.--Biographical materials, 1965-1966 (Box 127, Folder 1798)
      - Yung, C. T., President, 1959-1971 (Box 127, Folder 1799-1803)
      - Zietz, Miss, 1955 (Box 127, Folder 1804)
      - Campus Newsletter, 1973-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1805)
      - Chung Chi Journal, 1961-1969 (Box 129, Folder 1806)
      - Chung Chi Journal, 1969-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1807)
      - Yearbook, 1955, 1963 (Box 130, Folder 1808)
      - Chung Chi Bulletin, 1955-1956 (Box 131, Folder 1809)
      - Chung Chi Bulletin, 1967-1975 (Box 132, Folder 1810)
      - Chemistry Society Annual, 1958 (Box 132, Folder 1811)
      - Journal of the Department of Economics and Business Administration, 1959 (Box 132, Folder 1812)
      - New Horizons (published by UBCCC), 1952-1955 (Box 133, Folder 1819)
      - Brochures, 1955-1973, n.d. (Box 133, Folder 1813-1816)
      - Newspaper Articles, 1957-1976 (Box 133, Folder 1817)
      - Magazine Articles, 1960-1965 (Box 133, Folder 1818)
      - "Risk and Hope: The Hong Kong Story", 1956 (Box 133, Folder 1820)
      - "Story in Pictures", 1957, 1961 (Box 133, Folder 1821)
      - "Twenty Years of Growth", 1971 (Box 133, Folder 1822)
      - "A Quarter Century of Hong Kong", 1976 (Box 133, Folder 1823)
      - General, 1955-1962 (Box 133, Folder 1824)
    - Hong Kong Baptist College
      - President's Report, 1971-1980 (Box 134, Folder 1825)
      - Special Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 134, Folder 1826)
      - Catalogues, 1966-1978 (Box 134, Folder 1827)
      - College Directory, 1978-1979 (Box 134, Folder 1828)
      - Civil Engineering Department, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 1829)
      - Communications, 1974-1976 (Box 134, Folder 1830)
      - Division of Extramural Studies, 1976 (Box 134, Folder 1831)
      - Special Events, 1972-1977 (Box 134, Folder 1832)
      - Social Research Centre Evaluation: "Banting Occupational Prestige in Hong Kong", 1977 (Box 134, Folder 1833)
      - Academic Journal, 1977 (Box 135, Folder 1834)
      - Journal of Business and Economics, 1974 (Box 135, Folder 1835)
      - College News, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 1836)
      - Newsette, 1977-1979 (Box 135, Folder 1837)
      - Newsletter, Communication Department, 1971-1973 (Box 135, Folder 1838)
      - Our College, 1969-1976 (Box 135, Folder 1839)
      - Photojournalism, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 1840)
      - Journal of Science and Engineering, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 1841)
      - Miscellaneous Pamphlets and Booklets, 1974-1978, n.d. (Box 135, Folder 1842)
  - India
    - Ewing Christian College
      - Ewing Christian College Magazine, 1971-1978 (Box 136, Folder 1843)
      - Alumni Bulletin, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 1844)
      - Journal of Ewing College Chemical Society, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 1845)
      - Brochure, n.d. (Box 136, Folder 1846)
  - Indonesia
    - Christian University of Indonesia
      - Annual Report, 1970-1974 (Box 137, Folder 1847)
      - Report of the Rector and Message of the Chairman of the Board, 1971 (Box 137, Folder 1848)
      - Statement by I. P. Simandjuntak, 1954 (Box 137, Folder 1849)
      - Progress Report, 1954 (Box 137, Folder 1850a)
      - Reports on Visit by William Fenn, 1956 (Box 137, Folder 1580b)
      - Report to National Council of Churches in Indonesia, 1964 (Box 137, Folder 1851a)
      - Committee Work, 1955 (Box 137, Folder 1851b)
      - Building Projects, 1965 (Box 137, Folder 1852)
      - Reports--Medical Faculty, 1969, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 1853)
      - Medical College--Buildings and Equipment, 1971, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 1854)
      - Medical College Faculty, 1965-1966 (Box 137, Folder 1855)
      - Medical Faculty Buildings Program, n.d. (Box 137, Folder 1856)
      - Statistics, 1966 (Box 137, Folder 1857)
      - Application for a Language Laboratory, 1973 (Box 137, Folder 1858)
      - "Asian Christian Universities in Gear With National Development", 1970 (Box 137, Folder 1859)
    - Christian University of Indonesia
      - Bulletin, 1968-1970 (Box 138, Folder 1860)
      - Newsletter, 1968 (Box 138, Folder 1861)
      - Bulletin Research Ekonomi U.R.I., 1969-1973 (Box 138, Folder 1862)
      - Miscellaneous Publications in Indonesian, 1960-1969 (Box 138, Folder 1863)
      - Pamphlet, 1963 (Box 138, Folder 1864)
    - Petra Christian University
      - "Economic Impacts of Growth Centre on Surrounding Rural Villages", 1976 (Box 139, Folder 1865)
      - Team "Low Cost Housing Survey", 1977 (Box 139, Folder 1866)
      - "Effectivity of Credit Grants on Handiwork and Mining Sectors", 1979 (Box 139, Folder 1867)
      - Miscellaneous Publications in Indonesian, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 1868)
      - Bulletin, 1975-1979 (Box 139, Folder 1869)
    - Satya Watjana
      - Reports, 1961-1975, n.d. (Box 140, Folder 1870-1873)
      - Catalogue, 1976 (Box 141, Folder 1874)
      - Report on Special Intensive Indonesian Course, 1975 (Box 141, Folder 1875)
      - "Changes in Rice Farming in Selected Areas of Asia", 1972 (Box 141, Folder 1876)
      - Textbooks translated into Indonesian, 1972-1973 (Box 141, Folder 1877)
      - Notohamidjojo, Dr. O., "Kreativitas yang Bertanggung Jawab", 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1878)
      - Notohamidjojo, Dr. O., "Masalah: Keadilan", n.d. (Box 141, Folder 1879)
      - Essays by Students (in Indonesian), 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1880)
      - "Industrialisasi den Pendidikan", 1973 (Box 141, Folder 1881)
      - Report: "Guidance for Growth in Indonesia", 1973-1975 (Box 141, Folder 1882)
      - Proceedings of First Seminar in Aquatic Biology and Aquatic Hanagement of Rawa Pening Lake, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 1883)
      - Beran Visit, 1969 (Box 142, Folder 1884)
      - Buildings, 1959-1971, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 1885-1886)
      - Cooley, Frank, 1961-1965, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 1887)
      - Exchange Students, 1966 (Box 142, Folder 1888)
      - Faculty, 1961-1974 (Box 142, Folder 1889)
      - Faculty Housing, 1969-1972 (Box 142, Folder 1890)
      - Faculty--Overseas Personnel, 1961-1972 (Box 142, Folder 1891)
      - Fellowships, 1962-1973 (Box 142, Folder 1892-1893)
      - Finance, 1960-1971 (Box 142, Folder 1894-1897)
      - General Information, 1956-1974, n.d. (Box 142, Folder 1898-1900)
      - Hadiatmadja, Soenarto, 1969 (Box 143, Folder 1901)
      - Haaskonda, Towa Pala, 1963-1967 (Box 143, Folder 1902-1904)
      - Jenson, Kenneth and Norma, 1967-1971, n.d. (Box 143, Folder 1905-1910)
      - Kana, Nicodemus L., 1963-1972 (Box 143, Folder 1911-1912)
      - Ring, Douglas and Annie, 1965-1971 (Box 143, Folder 1913-1914)
      - Library, 1961-1972 (Box 143, Folder 1915)
      - Notohamidjojo, Dr. O, 1957-1971 (Box 144, Folder 1916-1918)
      - Oey, Pek Hoa (Elga), 1965 (Box 144, Folder 1919)
      - Printing Press Project, 1962-1972, n.d. (Box 144, Folder 1920-1921)
      - Research Institute, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 1922)
      - Scholarships, 1966-1975 (Box 144, Folder 1923)
      - Soegeng, Reksodihardjo, 1963-1965 (Box 144, Folder 1924)
      - Statistics, 1961-1970 (Box 144, Folder 1925)
      - Subanu, Surati, 1961-1971 (Box 144, Folder 1926-1928)
      - Sumarga, Christian H., 1972-1974 (Box 144, Folder 1929)
      - Suyitno (Soejitno), Amin, 1963-1972 (Box 144, Folder 1930)
      - Tanutama, T. A. (Tan Ree Hian), 1966-1971 (Box 145, Folder 1931-1933)
      - Tenth Anniversary, 1966 (Box 145, Folder 1934)
      - Tjahjakartana, Otniel (Liem Ding-Hian), 1968-1971 (Box 145, Folder 1935-1937)
      - Visitors, 1963 (Box 145, Folder 1938)
      - Wasis, Sastroredja, 1960-1971 (Box 145, Folder 1939-1941)
      - Wilardjo, Liet, 1965-1971 (Box 145, Folder 1942-1943)
      - Zachariaa, Joel C., 1963-1972 (Box 145, Folder 1944-1945)
      - Gema Bimbingan, 1974 (Box 146, Folder 1946)
      - Public Affairs Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 1947)
      - Seri Butu Pambimbingan (Box 146, Folder 1947)
      - Satya Wajana Research, 1977-1978 (Box 146, Folder 1948)
      - Morning Star, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 1949)
      - Semester Review, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 1950)
      - Warta, 1969-1979 (Box 146, Folder 1951)
      - Satya Watjana Salatiga, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 1952)
      - Satya Wajana Christian University and Teacher Training Institute, 1973 (Box 146, Folder 1953)
      - Satya Wajana: Facts and Prospects, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 1954)
      - Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 1955)
  - Japan
    - International Christian University
      - Business Finance, 1963 (Box 147, Folder 1956)
      - Bulletin, 1963-1978 (Box 147, Folder 1957)
      - Year Abroad Program, 1969-1970 (Box 147, Folder 1958)
      - Asian Cultural Studies, 1977-1979 (Box 147, Folder 1959)
      - Pamphlets, 1973, n.d. (Box 147, Folder 1960)
  - Korea
    - Ewha Womans University
      - Committee Minutes, 1946-1948 (Box 148, Folder 1961)
      - Bulletin, 1966 (Box 148, Folder 1962)
      - "The Role of Women in the Next Half Century", 1968 (Box 148, Folder 1963)
      - Report on "The Self-Study Survey of Ewha Womans University", 1961 (Box 148, Folder 1964)
      - Ewha Voice, 1973-1981 (Box 148, Folder 1965)
      - Journal of Korean Cultural Research Institute, 1971 (Box 148, Folder 1966)
      - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1936 (Box 148, Folder 1967)
      - Eightieth Anniversary, 1966 (Box 148, Folder 1968)
      - Pamphlet, 1979-1980 (Box 148, Folder 1969)
    - Soong Jun University
      - Annual Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 149, Folder 1970)